[Theme song]
[Rhythmic music]
(Reporter 1)
Between Babel Group and the prosecution
Are you saying there was collusion?
[Reporters are noisy]
(Reporter 2)
Please say something!
Please ask formal questions in writing
From now on, let’s talk about CEO Hong Cha-young.
Excessive questions
It will be considered assault.
Please get out of the way
(Vincenzo)
Let's go, lawyer.
(Reporter 3)
CEO
[Reporters are noisy]
[Meaningful music]
(Chinese book)
Brother
No, bro, those
Why do you keep watching?
Can't we just dispose of it all?
(Junwoo)
I've never seen it
(Chinese book)
Yes?
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Junwoo)
I never saw it
They're smart and that's what happened to us.
Brother, then…
Then
Shouldn’t it have been handled sooner?
such a good partner
Why are you processing it already?
Partner?
A sparring partner who makes me stronger
The moment I deal with Vincenzo
When I completely beat Vincenzo
[Chayoung sighs in frustration]
(Chayoung)
The more I think about it, the more it’s such a waste.
[Rhythmic music plays]
I was able to make an investment agreement.
Oh Gyeong-ja to the bank president
I'm satisfied with getting revenge.
1 to 1 is not a bad score
[Game sound plays]
Fire!
(Chayoung)
Oh, by the way
I'm going to see Kyeongja Oh tomorrow.
Do you want to go together?
I looked at the time.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, I'm single too
Write, why not?
At this point we again
There's one thing I need to focus on
You mean the real boss of Babel?
(Chayoung)
If the barbell stumbles
I thought I would show myself
It extends life again.
(Vincenzo)
Actually more evil than good
Recovery is several times faster
The restored evil becomes stronger
What kind of rice cake should I use?
Can you bring out the real boss?
[Meaningful music]
invisible equator
Mistakes leave traces
I need to find it
Starting today, Babel’s real boss
For short, let’s just call it ‘fool’.
That's nice, idiot.
[The dart sticks in]
[sigh]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(doctor)
If you have a family
I think you should tell us quickly.
[Calm music]
Those with a history of cancer
I need to take better care of it, but it’s a shame.
Have you ever had cancer before?
(doctor)
Yes, I have a history of lung cancer.
When is that?
(doctor)
Uh, in January 1993
You received your first diagnosis.
It was stage 3 at the time.
No surgery after 4 years
It appears that you have fully recovered.
(doctor)
It was stage 3, but you recovered completely without surgery.
It's truly a miracle
(Vincenzo)
I was diagnosed with lung cancer in January 1993.
I was left at an orphanage in May 1993.
Did you really abandon me because of your illness?
Do you think you'll die leaving me behind?
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
(Cheolwook)
There's no one today
(Yeonjin)
That's right
Everyone has no patience, no patience
[Interesting music]
[Footsteps are heard]
[Metal detector operating sound]
(in advance)
I think
Looks like there
[Exciting music]
That's a person
It's the place that most people don't go to.
(Heesu)
That's right
But the boss
Are you out to rob the safe?
Why did you bring the stethoscope again?
(Heesu)
Ah, it feels empty just to come out.
Are you okay? huh?
[Larry Kang sighs]
First of all, okay? let's find gold
- (Larry Kang) Oh, quiet.
- Shhh!
[Yeonjin sighs]
(Yeonjin)
They live really hard
(Cheolwook)
Still, there are no monks
After all, true Buddhists are different.
[Interesting music]
(Chae Shin)
head monk
But even with this water vein pole
Can you find gold?
(dropping)
Like a water vein
Even gold has something called Qi.
So with this water vein pole
That means you can know it.
(Chae Shin)
Ah, yes
I, but, I
[moktak sound effect]
Is it okay for us to covet material things like this?
Are you greedy for material things?
Even if I look for gold
We won't take a penny
Don't you know?
(Chae Shin)
yes
For children suffering from rare diseases
Everyone decided to donate
(dropping)
We are not greedy for material things.
I want to practice Buddha's mercy.
Okay, monk.
[Chae-shin’s surprised moan]
[dark music]
(dropping)
What's going on?
(Chae Shin)
'Messenger of Hell'
I stepped on the card, monk.
You've got to go back, you Western bastard!
[Chae-shin's angry groan]
[mumbling]
(Chae Shin)
[surprised]
Monk!
[Monks’ surprised moans]
[Meaningful music]
[Chae-shin’s surprised moan]
[Dove cries]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Italian]
Again! also!
[Speaks Italian]
[Vincenzo’s angry groan]
[Korean]
Oh, what a surprise.
[sigh]
[Interesting music]
go
Go, go!
[Italian]
please go
I'm begging you
[Dove cries]
[sigh]
Disappear! go!
go away! go away! go away…
[Korean]
Choosing your location is one thing.
It's really amazing.
You like this spot, right?
[humorous music]
Okay, okay, so
Don't cry only when I'm sleeping
okay? please
[sigh]
Your name from now on
It's kind
[Interesting music]
Hey, Insagi, don't cry, okay?
[Dove cries]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(police)
Are you here?
[Car door slams shut]
[Meaningful music]
(Junwoo)
Are you Director Gil Jong-moon?
[laughter]
(Myunghee)
yes
Terminate your contract with us
I immediately requested personal protection from the prosecution.
What kind of deal are you trying to make with the prosecution?
(Seunghyuk)
Well, that’s not it yet
No information available
[sigh]
Who is the prosecutor in charge?
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
(Myunghee)
Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
This is prosecutor Jeong In-guk.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
If you are here...
(Junwoo)
Jeong In-guk?
Where have you heard this name before?
[Prosecutor Jeong speaks]
(Myunghee)
When my father was president
Babel was targeted for investigation
You are a troublesome person, right?
(Myunghee)
Yeah, I don't listen to anyone
I don’t listen to the chief prosecutor.
I don't listen to the district prosecutor's words.
I built a wall around both my ears
It has the nickname ‘Byeokbyeok’.
(Seunghyuk)
yes
He was demoted and went down to Mokpo.
It was posted last week
AC, really
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Junwoo clears his throat]
Yes, I am lawyer Jang Jun-woo.
(Director Gil)
My name is Director Gil Jong-moon.
[Meaningful music]
Director Gil
(Junwoo)
Why is this happening between us?
(Director Gil)
I have some requests from the Chairman.
Tell me anything, I'll listen to it all
(Director Gil)
For now
You're not killing me.
(Junwoo)
When did I try to kill the director?
(Director Gil)
I'm going to kill you soon
Anyone who knows the president's face
Because I'm the only one
[Sharp sound effect]
(Junwoo)
Okay
All I have to do is promise not to kill him, right?
(Director Gil)
30 million US dollars
Please send it to the account I tell you.
Once payment is confirmed
I'm leaving this country without a word
If you don't give it to me
Chairman's identity
Even what I did to my father
I'll tell the prosecutor
Ah, I got it, that
[nervous music]
account number
(Junwoo)
no
Send me a text message
And Thirty Million Dollars
It takes several days to launder money and remit it.
(Seunghyuk)
Thirty Million…
(Junwoo)
You know that, right?
[Myunghee’s surprised gasp]
Yes, Director, I will contact you.
Are you asking for thirty million dollars?
(Myunghee)
Ha, holy shit, really.
[Music that heightens the mood]
[The pen falls down]
Don't you eat it?
Why do you eat such burnt food?
bad for your health
(Chayoung)
This is okay
Now
Try eating the non-burned side.
delicious
Well, just eat the side that isn't completely burnt.
Tsk, it'll be fine, whatever.
(Joosung)
[Mounting]
This is the printed data.
(Chayoung)
oh, thank you
(Vincenzo)
thank you
(Chayoung)
in police records
This is information from Chairman Jang Han-seo’s older brother, Jang Han-seok.
My American name is Henry Zhang.
[humorous music]
(Vincenzo)
um
(Joosung)
[Laughing]
fool
What?
Then, Chairman Jang Han-seo’s older brother.
Are you stupid?
(Chayoung)
I'm not sure if he's stupid
Well, let's start by investigating the surroundings.
(Vincenzo)
After leaving the United States 15 years ago
There is no record of entering Korea?
After graduating from art school, I continued to work as an artist.
(Chayoung)
Current whereabouts are unknown.
(Joosung)
Ha, I live as a free man
I guess you're not interested in business?
When did Chairman Jang Kook-hwan pass away?
2 years ago
Then at my father’s funeral
I'm saying you didn't come.
(Joosung)
No, I have to pay for my father’s funeral.
It's like sliced like this.
(Chayoung)
Oh no!
You should not eat sweet potatoes when doing important work.
It means my throat gets clogged.
[Interesting music]
[Vincenzo’s sneer]
Isn’t that a superstition?
[Chayoung’s refreshing groan]
(Chayoung)
Me
Every time I take an important test
I mean I didn’t eat seaweed soup.
Thanks to you, I passed everything
But I ate 100 sweet potatoes.
A place where you can’t drink cider
Aren’t barbells and idols?
It's there
Ah, I feel uncomfortable, I don’t want to eat it.
I'm going to Oh Kyeong-ja.
(Joosung)
Babel Pharmaceutical's bereaved families made an appointment in the evening.
don't forget
Ah, today. See you later.
Ah
[The door slams shut]
Oh Gyeong-ja
(Joosung)
I've searched everywhere
[Blows out air]
Well, not really
No family to contact, yeah
If you have at least one child
It would be so much better, ugh.
No, I won't go even if I do.
There are a lot more bastards like that, huh?
[Interesting music]
It's no use raising them all, you bastards.
You will be punished, you bastards.
Don't you eat it?
Yes, I should eat it all.
[Joosung’s laughter]
Manager
yes
Let’s eat cleanly.
Wipe your mouth and the sides of your mouth.
thank you so much
[Humorous sound effects]
It's messy, really
(Joosung)
Because I can’t eat cleanly like the lawyer.
I'm really sorry
(Gyeongja)
I feel really refreshed inside.
Every corner of that damn house
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Gyeongja’s laughter]
[sigh]
thank you so much
(Chayoung)
Attorney Vincenzo did it all.
I only help a little
[laughter]
Thanks to you, I am so enraged
Looks like you're doing well
(Chayoung)
This hospital room is also occupied by Attorney Vincenzo.
You are paying for it.
Oh, what should I do about this? I’m sorry.
I'm too embarrassed to stay here any longer.
[groaning in denial]
[Gyeongja sighs]
[Approaching footsteps]
(Gyeongja)
yes, hello
(doctor)
Are you in some uncomfortable place?
(Gyeongja)
None
(doctor)
I can't take painkillers at night.
I heard you said that?
Ah, there
If I get hit by that, I feel a little nauseous.
I can handle it just fine without it.
(doctor)
Then do whatever you feel comfortable with.
(Vincenzo)
What do you do for comfort?
What kind of resort room is this?
Do what’s convenient for the patient?
[Vincenzo puts down his bag]
No, I didn't mean that.
(Vincenzo)
and
Did the patient eat well?
[bright music]
directly with your eyes
Shouldn’t you check it?
Look
Didn't the patient eat anything?
I just wanted to ask you
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Vincenzo)
And what kind of side dish is this?
Are you just giving this to the patient to eat?
Would you eat this?
(doctor)
Because I am not a nutritionist.
Until that...
You're a doctor, not a nutritionist, right? But
The patient told me not to give it
What if I don't prescribe painkillers?
(Gyeongja)
That's me...
(Vincenzo)
Mr. Oh Gyeong-ja, please stay still!
(doctor)
I think you are experiencing severe side effects.
Let’s put it on hold for now…
The patient's condition is like this now.
What a hold!
(Chayoung)
Okay, that's enough.
Are you suddenly angry out of nowhere?
Ms. Oh Gyeong-ja
(Vincenzo)
If you are going to do whatever you want like this
Why are you in the hospital?
[screaming]
Yes?
Don't be stubborn in the future.
Just do what the hospital tells you to do.
yes
(Chayoung)
Lawyer
Oh, sorry, sorry.
[Chayoung sighs]
Please understand
There are a lot of things I'm a bit sensitive to these days.
It's scary though
Strangely, I feel good
[Meaningful music]
(Chinese book)
Brother, I started in the morning
Same, I had a meeting with the president of Taesan Bank.
Both banks are in Babel
I have no intention of investing at all.
(Junwoo)
Even though you signed an investment agreement with Shinkwang Bank?
yes
Hong Cha-young told reporters yesterday
Because of talking about it
(Chinese book)
You can't trust Babel
This is my position, brother.
No, I mean
Vincenzo and Hong Cha-young
I wish I had dealt with that from the beginning...
(Junwoo)
Shut it!
Oh, I'm purely
I'm thinking on your side!
Don't raise your voice
You keep saying that, it's scary, bro.
Sorry, brother.
(Junwoo)
For now
Tonight with the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
I'll make a place for you
Come on time
yes, i understand
[Call end sound]
[Throws away cell phone]
[sigh]
Ha, my father
The person who let go so easily, Mr.
[laughter]
[Button operation sound]
(Chinese book)
Connect with Director Lee of the Strategy Office
(people)
thank you
[Calm music plays]
(Chayoung)
Wow, it looks really delicious
(Victim’s family 1)
thank you
No, we
I set up a Chinese restaurant in the hotel.
The manager changed the location.
(Joosung)
This is a really good restaurant, huh?
Try this, it's really here
[Joosung’s savoring moans]
TV is not allowed here
[People laughing]
[Blows out air]
[Chayoung’s elasticity]
(Chayoung)
Um, wow, that's awesome.
Just above your head
It looks like the CG of flying stars is rising.
[People laughing]
This is it, what should I say?
[Rolling tongue]
tomato pasta flavor
A taste of Vincenzo Cassano's hometown
[Juseong’s elasticity]
[People laughing]
(Victim’s family 2)
I should have brought you here a long time ago.
I'm so sorry I'm late
Don't say anything
[Laughs slightly]
But
There was a small disturbance last week
I heard
yes
Babel Pharmaceutical stock investors
Because of us
They say their stocks are trash
[Calm music]
(Victim's family 3)
He came to our meeting and caused a scene.
(Victim's family 4)
Luckily, I got all the criticism I could eat for the rest of my life.
Well organized
[Chayoung sighs]
(Chayoung)
They really are sociopaths.
Without even thinking about the unfair people
Mr. Lee, tsk!
(Victim’s family 1)
‘I’m bored, stop it’
‘Stop it, Goinpal’
Now, well, we're just going to do it.
I can't do that.
(Chayoung)
If something unfair happens to you
Please contact me anytime
I'll help you right away
[People laughing]
thank you
(Joosung)
Try it, it’s a really delicious restaurant.
[People laughing]
(Chinese book)
I should have brought you something a long time ago.
I was a little out of my mind.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
I think you must have been out of your mind.
The company is running in such a mess.
[Laughing]
Yeah, I fell short.
Please go forward
I hope you become a good partner
(Director Seo)
Well, I think you're confusing something.
We are not partners, we are in a contractual relationship.
Understanding each other is important for a long time.
This is it
(Seunghyuk)
Manager Seo?
[Seunghyuk’s embarrassed laughter]
(Chinese book)
to ensure that
I have expressed my sincerity sufficiently, but
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
I showed some sincerity
Don't be so condescending
[Meaningful music]
If you are rude to us
You can insert the barbell at any time.
Do you understand?
Yes, I will keep that in mind.
[Myunghee’s laughter]
'Cause now you're in the same boat
Please say a word of thanks, Chief Prosecutor.
Ah, Choi Myung-hee, you acted so strong.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Are you now a salesperson in Seocho-dong?
It suits you, hey
[Myunghee and Chief Prosecutor Hwang laugh]
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, really today
Like this, a historic day
I don't think so
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
Right, Chief Prosecutor, yes?
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang laughs]
Will it be a glorious history?
Will it be a history of shame?
(Director Seo)
We'll see
Moving forward humbly
I'll do my best
Thank you very much
[groaning in denial]
Don't try your best
It's a burden
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang and Hanseo laugh]
yes, i understand
(Chinese book)
Chief Prosecutor, let me have a drink.
Can I upload it?
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Just looking at it, I feel like I’m about the same age as my uncle.
Can I take it with one hand?
(Chinese book)
Oh, yeah, sure, yeah
[Sound of clinking glasses plays]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Um, can I give Manager Seo a drink too?
Ah, why are the old guys like this?
I can't come to my senses
[laughter]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
No, how do you normally
Do you drink alcohol often?
(Chinese book)
I'm not good at it, but I enjoy it.
Yes, then please enter carefully.
Chief Prosecutor, Chief Prosecutor
Uh, yes, Chairman Jang.
If you need anything
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Choi Myung-hee behind me, that Seocho-dong salesperson
Tell it to me through him
Huh? okay?
- Yes, I understand, yes.
- (Chief Prosecutor Hwang) Okay, good job.
let's go
[Car starting sound]
(Chinese book)
Please go in
(Seunghyuk and Myunghee)
Shall we have a party afterward?
follow my car
[Meaningful music]
Yes?
[Car door opens]
What are we going to do?
Well, what
[Car door slams shut]
If you want to follow me, I have to follow you, let's go
[Myunghee’s sigh]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Choi Myung-hee is
I'm a salesperson in Seocho-dong.
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang and Director Seo laugh]
So all you have to do is hold on to him
He, just watch over him
[Director Seo’s disapproving groan]
(Director Seo)
Still, there are times when it's beneath us
It's so much better, like...
[Director Seo’s disapproving groan]
[tire rubbing sound]
- (Manager Seo) What is it?
- (Chief Prosecutor Hwang) Hey, you bastard, are you crazy?
- (Manager Seo) Don’t you drive properly?
- (Article) Sorry
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
What are those bastards?
[nervous music]
(Director Seo)
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing now?
- (Chief Prosecutor Hwang) Hey, what are these, what are these?
- (Director Seo) Huh?
[People moan in surprise]
[The knight’s powerful groan]
(article)
Let go, Lee!
[The knight groans with difficulty]
(Director Seo)
These bastards, what are these bastards?
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Hey, what are you guys
Do you know who we are? Man
Hey, you bastard!
[Exciting music]
[Yeonjin’s surprised moan]
Maybe
Those bastards, that
You're not a thief, are you a thief?
Attorney Vincenzo, you must have a lot of valuables.
I'm watching you well
I'll go to the store and get the master key.
(Yeonjin)
Me?
[Yeonjin’s surprised moan]
(Cheolwook)
Take care of yourself
[nervous music]
[Gangman 1’s surprised groan]
[Interesting music]
(Cheolwook)
I don't want to hurt you guys.
just go
(Yeonjin)
Haha, you bastards of thieves, this, huh?
I have nothing to do
Do sacred work, man! uh?
labor
[Gangman 1’s powerful moans]
[Yeonjin’s scream]
(Cheolwook)
Uh, honey!
(Yeonjin)
Honey!
(Cheolwook)
How dare my wife…
[Putting down the detector]
Yeonjin-ah
[Splendid music]
I just can't stand it today
(Cheolwook)
Instead, I will only use 10% of my martial arts skills.
[There is a crunching sound]
Honey, no!
[Cheolwook’s spirit]
[Gangman 1’s groans of difficulty]
[Gangman 2’s powerful moans]
[Cheolwook’s groans of difficulty]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Interesting music]
[in a difficult voice]
Please save me
(Cheolwook)
Did you know you would say that, Mr. Lee!
Boy, your ears are exposed
[Cheolwook’s surprised groan]
This bastard!
Hey, hey, hey, let’s go in!
[Cheolwook’s spirit]
[Gangman 1’s groans of difficulty]
[Cheolwook’s elasticity]
(Yeonjin)
It's been a while for me too
Let’s try some hip extensions!
[Yeonjin’s powerful moans]
[Yeonjin’s spirit]
[Gangster 2’s heavy groans]
clean
[Yeonjin’s spirit]
[There is a crunching sound]
And jerk!
[Cheolwook’s elasticity]
(Cheolwook)
Oh, nice, nice, nice! uh?
[Kiss Cheolwook’s side]
Yeonjin is alive!
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
These kids
[Cheolwook speaks]
(Yeonjin)
Huh?
[Cheolwook and Yeonjin moan in surprise]
[Cheolwook and Yeonjin are chortling]
- (Cheolwook) Honey, honey
- (Yeonjin) Honey
(Cheolwook)
Uh, uh, caught.
(Yeonjin)
AC, you bastard!
[Cheolwook’s groans of difficulty]
(Victim's family 3)
Oh my
[Chayoung’s laughter]
(Chayoung)
See you again when it gets warmer.
Let's go on an outing
(Victim's family 3)
Oh, it's still the four of us
I decided to go on a trip next week.
Towards Jindo
[People laughing]
[Chayoung’s elasticity]
Jin is good too
While you're gone, just one bottle of goji berry liquor.
Please do me a favor, yeah
[People laughing]
(Victim's family 3)
yes, yes
Have a nice trip
Have fun
(Victim's family 3)
yes
Lawyer
[Calm music]
thank you
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
Oh my
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
[People laughing]
[Victim’s family 3 pats his back]
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Have a nice trip
(Victim's family 3)
yes
[People laughing]
(Victim’s family 1)
thank you
(Victims' families)
Thank you, thank you
- (Victim's Family 3) Thank you so much.
- (Chayoung) Yes
(Victim’s family 2)
Manager
(Victim’s family 1)
Oh, the manager too
(Vincenzo)
Okay, wow, Illo
(Victim’s family 1)
thank you
Thank you so much
[Meaningful music]
[People each say hello]
(Chayoung)
Have a nice trip
Bereaved families now
I hope only happy things happen
(Vincenzo)
I hope so too
I will never forget the pain for the rest of my life.
(Chayoung)
Of course it is.
I just hope to be covered in happiness
(Vincenzo)
Tsk
Come in
[Chayoung takes out the keys]
(Chayoung)
Thanks for taking me there.
You didn't take me there
I'm on my way to buy wine.
Right across from Geumga Plaza
Is there a big wine shop?
Oh, they don't have the wine I'm looking for there.
So at the intersection in front of here
I'm on my way to the wine shop.
Is it time to close the door now?
Then you can buy it tomorrow.
[A dog barks in the distance]
Take a break
[Meaningful music]
[laughter]
[clings the keys]
[The door bursts open]
[The door slams shut]
[Switch operation sound]
[nervous music]
[screaming]
(Chayoung)
Wait a minute, wait a minute! no
No, out of all the things, why a hammer?
[Ancient music]
In case you don't know, I'm a Jew.
3rd degree Taekwondo, 2nd degree Jiu-Jitsu, 2nd degree Hapkido
Total is 8 levels!
(Ghost 3)
7th gear
Uh, yes, 7th gear, 3rd, 2nd, 2nd, 7th gear!
So don't act awkwardly!
[nervous music]
Oh, don't come! Don't come, don't come!
Hey, don't come!
[Chayoung’s scream]
[Gangman 3’s harsh moans]
Hey, what should I do? Hey, don't come, don't come!
Oh, don't come, don't come
[Chayoung’s scream]
[Gangman 3’s harsh moans]
(Ghost 4)
Hey, we're in big trouble!
(Ghost 3)
What is it?
[Gangman 4’s heavy groans]
(Vincenzo)
It's me
[Gangman 4’s heavy groans]
[The gangsters’ groans of difficulty]
[Exciting music]
Oh my!
(Chayoung)
Hey, hey!
[Gangman 4 groans in pain]
[Gangman 3’s powerful moans]
[Gangster 3’s groans of difficulty]
[Chayoung’s spirit]
(Vincenzo)
Uh, uh
What is this?
[Vincenzo laughs]
Go scratch my back, go over there
no
If you're going to follow me, you have to be discreet.
[Meaningful music]
The kid is insincere.
Huh?
- (Juseong) Let’s go.
- (Chayoung) Yes
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Gangster 3’s groans of difficulty]
Are you okay?
[Gangman 3’s angry groans]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Vincenzo’s angry groan]
(Chayoung)
Uh, uh, wait, wait!
Oh, don't go, don't go
It's because I'm scared when I'm alone
(Vincenzo)
No, find out who sent it.
I have to question it.
It's obvious, who sent it?
[Chayoung’s groans of difficulty]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
(Chayoung)
Ah, why are you like this?
I guess I ate less steamed chicken
I have no strength in my legs
[Rough breathing]
[Meaningful music]
[Switch operation sound]
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang groans with difficulty]
(Seunghyuk)
Chief Prosecutor?
[Hanseo’s laughter]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Hey, Chairman Jang
(Chinese book)
Yes, it’s me, Chairman Jang.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
you
Do you know what you are doing?
Current district prosecutors and chief prosecutors
It was kidnapping, kidnapping!
(Chinese book)
So, you should have judged the situation well earlier.
Well, are you coming?
You know people very rudely, right?
(Seunghyuk)
Chairman
Did Chairman Jang Jun-woo allow this?
Yes, just to understand
He told me to just scare him.
(Myunghee)
yes
[Hanseo’s laughter]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
you now
You're making a huge mistake
(Chinese book)
You guys are
I made a huge mistake
I hope you get the money
Aren’t we supposed to show respect and obedience?
hey!
You really want to get scolded!
(Director Seo)
Where did you get such clumsy pranks?
I know the barbell will be smashed starting tomorrow
Okay!
[laughter]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Tsk, hey, Choi Myung-hee, release it quickly, your arm hurts.
- Hey, CEO Han, solve it quickly!
- (Seunghyuk) Ah, yes
(Director Seo)
Ah, what are you doing!
Ugh, sit quietly.
Why is it so hard for you guys?
[Tense sound effect]
[nervous music]
[Junwoo is humming]
What is this again?
[People's surprised gasps]
[Heavy sound effect]
[Junwoo’s elasticity]
[Myunghee and Seunghyuk’s surprised gasps]
[Junwoo is humming]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
[There is a crackling sound]
[Heavy sound effect]
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang’s urgent groan]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Please save me, save me!
Please save me
Uh, Chairman.
Please save me, Chairman, please save me.
[shaking breathing]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
(Junwoo)
[in a high voice]
Is he dead?
Next is
[Junwoo laughs]
[Junwoo sighs]
[Junwoo is humming]
[shaking breathing]
[Tense sound effect]
[Junwoo sighs]
I won't kill you first
Who's next?
[shaking breathing]
in italy
Your son is terrible at soccer!
Chairman! Chairman!
I, I was arrogant.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Please forgive me
I was wrong!
Chairman, I respect you.
I'm like this, like this, Chairman.
So, I respect you, Chairman.
[nervous music]
Respectfully, please save my son.
Please save me, please save me
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang sobs]
Yes, yes, that is!
So, from the beginning
Kinda...
You're good, huh?
[Awkward laughter]
[Junwoo’s laughter]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
[Meaningful music]
[Junwoo is humming]
(Chinese book)
Please tell me in advance
Is that so, brother?
Surprise!
It's good, right?
Although this is a presumptuous statement,
really later
could be a big problem
The biggest problem for me is
[nervous music]
All I can do is hurt my feelings
[Strong moan]
Sir, why isn’t it cleaned like this!
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
Everything from today
I'll put it back in its place
(Junwoo)
And what is the price
I'll show you clearly
I will follow the Chairman's instructions carefully.
I will follow you diligently too.
yes, yes
(Junwoo)
Okay
Ah!
Ah, our Hanseo, our Hanseo
You should strengthen your security personnel first.
'Cause you're my Achilles heel
Yes, yes, I understand, brother.
[Meaningful music]
[radio operation sound]
[A siren is heard]
It would either be Babel or an idol.
Who gave the instructions?
It seems like someone's independent order
Something is urgent and clumsy.
Who on earth…
Do you think that if you kill me, everything will end?
I'm not trying to kill you
Making you unable to use your body at all
That must have been the purpose
Yes?
You heard the hammer
(Vincenzo)
If the goal was to kill
wrap a rope around your neck
Either stab me in the stomach with a knife or…
Oh, stop, stop, stop
[Clears cough]
I'm somewhere else today
The window is broken and it's hard to put your mind at ease.
Yes, I'll be at my friend's house.
Yeah, that would be nice.
[Chayoung sighs]
What are you doing?
Walk
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
(Vincenzo)
No way
[humorous music]
Can't you?
[Call end sound]
(Vincenzo)
don't even dream
[Call connection tone]
[Guidance voice]
Now the customer
I can't answer the phone
Please call again next time
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Call connection tone]
(acquaintance)
Oh, what should I do?
I have an all-night service later
[Call end sound]
[Chayoung’s angry groan]
(Vincenzo)
It's been 30 minutes since I contacted you.
Not yet?
Tsk, no, whatever.
Looks like everyone is busy
Human relationships are yet to be restored.
I guess it's less.
You can just sleep at the hotel, okay?
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
Aren’t you scared of being alone?
[Chayoung’s laughter]
(Chayoung)
Are you scared?
Wow, I'm dumbfounded.
I look at something in vain
Do you think I'm hallucinating?
Looking at it from before, it seems like that might be the case.
(Chayoung)
Shhh, no, no
I was out of my mind earlier.
For now
I'm back with an iron mentality.
[laughter]
[Chayoung unfastens her seat belt]
You had a hard time today
thank you
[Vincenzo unfastens his seat belt]
[Fascinating music]
[The fascinating music stops]
(Vincenzo)
Please contact me if anything happens.
[Interesting music]
(Chayoung)
don't worry about me
[Vincenzo fastens his seat belt]
[Car engine sound]
[tire rubbing sound]
Chi
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Meaningful music]
(Employee 1)
welcome, welcome
[Employee 2’s bizarre laughter]
[Frightened groan]
IC
Why is everyone opening their eyes like that, huh?
[Drill operating sound]
Hey there
What are you doing here in my room?
Oh, there's a problem with the door lock.
I received a report.
Almost open all night
I almost fell asleep
[nervous music]
[Employee 3’s bizarre laughter]
[surprised moan]
[bizarre laughter]
[screaming]
[Chayoung’s scream]
Customer, you are done!
(Cheolwook)
[in a difficult voice]
sorry
[Lonely music]
(Yeonjin)
sorry
(Cheolwook)
Entering the house without permission
Oh, I'm sorry.
I am rather grateful
(Yeonjin)
Well, at first glance, he didn't look like a petty thief.
Mr. Lawyer
It feels like I'm just waiting
(Cheolwook)
I never thought the kids would have prepared gas guns.
[Cheolwook’s painful moans]
[Interesting music]
(Kiseok)
Even my intuition tells me it's a killer.
This man is clearly in danger.
(Hongsik)
Aren't they the ones sent by those guys?
Hey, what about Park Seok-do or Barbell?
Hey, I wish I did
They must have sent real professionals.
Well, if you get robbed by the pawn shop owner,
Isn't that a petty thief?
[Cheolwook’s heavy breathing]
It's a pro
The moment I caught it, I felt it.
[Cheolwook’s heavy breathing]
‘Oh, this guy, this isn’t normal.’
thank you
(Cheolwook)
yes
I won't be coming again now, okay?
(Vincenzo)
rest
(Yeonjin)
Uh, wait a minute, now, wait a minute.
[Moaning in pain]
(Yeonjin)
This
[Interesting music]
Take it and eat it, it's really delicious.
(Vincenzo)
no, i'm fine
(Yeonjin)
Baby, this is our robe, please eat it.
It's so delicious, this
(Vincenzo)
Oh yes, thank you
Ah…
[Laughing]
I will eat well
- (Yeonjin) Yes
- (Cheolwook) Boil it and eat it.
yes please go in
(Yeonjin)
Yes, I will.
(Cheolwook)
Come in, come in
[Cheolwook’s surprised groan]
(Yeonjin)
why
(Hongsik)
Oh my, where are you going?
[Cheolwook’s painful moans]
(Cheolwook)
I can't give up, it's okay
(Yeonjin)
Ah!
(Cheolwook)
Ah, these guys
He might be hiding somewhere right now
I'm that guy...
[Blows his mouth]
[Laughs slightly]
[The door slams shut]
[Switch operation sound]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Puts down the ramen]
[Dove cries]
[Sound of clinking food is heard]
[sigh]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[breathes and then exhales]
[Vincenzo’s surprised gasp]
[Magnificent music]
[Interesting music]
Hey, Insagi
(Vincenzo)
take your friend out quickly
Take your friends and get out quickly!
[Dove cries]
[Speaks Italian]
Insagi!
[angry moaning]
[Strong moan]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
[angry moaning]
[Rough breathing]
[Dark sound effect]
[Italian]
Why so fast?
shit!
[angry moaning]
[sigh]
[breathes and then exhales]
[A knocking sound is heard]
[Chayoung’s trembling breathing]
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
I'm scared, really scared
And it's so cold
[Chayoung’s trembling breathing]
Okay, I'll go in.
[Chayoung’s scream]
[Interesting music]
Uh, uh, it's so warm!
[Elasticity]
[Painful groan]
My feet tickle
[Chayoung’s painful moans]
[Chayoung sniffles]
[sigh]
I'll take care of you for just one day
[The door slams shut]
[laughter]
Do you really have to wear something like that to sleep?
this nightwear
Created to commemorate Bralo’s 80th anniversary…
- (Chayoung) Do you boil ramen?
- Yes
[Sniffles]
Do you also eat ramen or something?
(Vincenzo)
Yes, the pawn shop owner gave it to me.
Do you want to eat? Should I boil two?
(Chayoung)
I'm done
My face swells when I eat and sleep because I can't digest it.
Okay, then
[Vincenzo’s uncomfortable moans]
[Interesting music]
[Chayoung sniffles]
[Chayoung’s savoring moans]
(Chayoung)
A
overall
One serving of Korean ramen
I think it's less
By legally unifying
It needs to be strictly regulated.
It won't work, right?
Didn’t you say your face was swollen in the morning?
Just digest it well and sleep, okay?
[humorous music]
Didn’t you eat a lot for dinner earlier?
When something bad happens, my stomach hurts quickly.
Oh, yes, I guess you did.
(Chayoung)
But
What did I do like that again?
Are you saying you ate a lot for dinner?
Otherwise, that's okay.
I'll prepare your bed for you.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
Don't you eat it?
If this were Italy
The lawyer just…
Enjoy
Eat everything
[Satisfied groan]
(Chayoung)
Are you going to sleep here?
I'm sorry, what should I do?
I'm on the floor
Lawyer, you have to sleep on the sofa.
(Chayoung)
Oh my, oh my, manly
How are you two here?
There's a room over there
[Interesting music]
Let's go
(Chayoung)
So sweet!
[Magnificent music]
[Chayoung’s surprised moan]
What, is that, a chicken, what?
[Chayoung’s surprised exclamation]
[elegant music]
I'll take care of you just for today
I will stay there until my mind calms down.
(Chayoung)
no
I'll go as soon as the house is cleaned up.
I can't sleep because my eyes hurt.
Taste, indeed
(Vincenzo)
Ah
It wasn't me, it was the previous owner who did it.
Ah, you are free to go.
Be sure to buy two ramen noodles
I'll buy one box instead of two.
(Chayoung)
But
Can I ask two more questions today?
About the mafia
Just two
Are mafia bosses really scary?
It's cruel and there's no blood or tears, right?
Depends on the boss
The boss I served
He was a reasonable businessman.
I guess he was a very nice person?
(Vincenzo)
yes
To me
He was like a father to me.
Next question
(Chayoung)
Last time
People like in the movies
I told you that death can happen.
If you do something wrong, you have to pay the price.
It's the mafia's principles.
(Vincenzo)
yes
Then, perhaps it is in the hands of a lawyer.
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
Have you ever done it yourself?
Have you ever killed someone yourself?
no
I'm a lawyer
(Chayoung)
Right?
I couldn't believe it again
[Chayoung sighs]
Tsk
Even if you are a mafia lawyer
Would you kill someone?
If you have ever killed someone yourself
Are you going to break off the relationship?
(Chayoung)
Rather than that
just
Like a person in a distant world
I think I can feel it
In murals or faded newspapers
Like a stuffed person
If I am that kind of person to someone
I think it's a bit sad
But I
I want to live a life like that of a stuffed animal.
Why?
(Chayoung)
Ah
To people in life
Is that so you don't get hurt?
no
People ask me to lend them money
I have a lot
[laughter]
I thought there would be another great answer
It's a very real life mode.
The answer is finished, go to sleep now.
yes
[Chayoung sighs]
[Meaningful music]
[gunshot]
[Speaks Italian]
[surprised gasp]
[sigh]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Calm music]
[sigh]
(Chayoung)
Huh?
You know Prosecutor Seo Woong-ho, Southeastern District Prosecutors’ Office?
The district prosecutor's confidant
He died last night
[Meaningful music]
While drunk driving
I fell down the mountain
What happened to us yesterday
It's consistent, right?
no
Director Seo was completely defeated.
It's not clumsy
[sigh]
Looking at it
People are bleeding more and more
I think it will increase
(Junwoo)
Yeah, when are you coming to Korea?
Oh, okay, I understand.
[Junwoo puts down his phone]
(Chinese book)
Who is coming?
Ah
I want to know about Vincenzo.
I sent someone to Italy
Ah, yes
What did you find out?
You'll see when you come
[Laughs slightly]
yes
You were very surprised by my brother yesterday, right?
[nervous music]
No, I learned a lot yesterday too
[Laughs slightly]
yes
Starting today, I'm going to do it really perfectly.
Security personnel have been strengthened, right?
Yes, in case you are followed.
Operated by two teams
Okay
[Puts down chopsticks]
Hey bro
(Chinese book)
Uh…
I have something to tell you.
(Junwoo)
um
Looking at your expression, it looks like you did something wrong again?
[surprised gasp]
(Junwoo)
Who told you to do something like that?
who!
Sorry, brother, I
I'm just a brother
To ease your worries
Brother, I am
I have nothing but loyalty, brother.
Please believe, please believe...
Don't make excuses for your mistakes
Because it only makes those mistakes stand out.
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
[sigh]
[Puts down spoon]
[Call connection tone]
Why are you walking around Yeongtong awkwardly?
I miss you
Yeah? Tsk
See you later then
[Laughs slightly]
Have you gone to work yet?
I'm going to do it now
Are you really out of touch these days?
But
Is that your senior’s house?
I don’t think so?
(Vincenzo)
Ah
[Italian]
good morning
[Korean]
No, is it Attorney Vincenzo’s house?
Why are you there?
I slept here
(Junwoo)
Yes?
I have to go to work, call me later
Ah, stand, stand…
[Call end sound]
[sigh]
[Puts down the phone]
[nervous music]
[Car remote control operation sound]
(Kiseok)
Attorney Vincenzo
Here it is
[surprised moan]
Ah, yes
[Strong moan]
[Exciting music]
(Kiseok)
I don't know what it is
Are you in danger now?
I see right through it.
Yes?
My contact…
This is my contact information
If there is a dangerous situation
Please contact us anytime
simply by text
You can send ‘Help Me’
(Vincenzo)
yes
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Embarrassed laughter]
You may have noticed, but in fact, I
[Laughs slightly]
[Lonely music]
Yes, not a kitchen assistant
(Kiseok)
Just know that
It goes naturally
naturally
[Humorous sound effects]
[Moaning in pain]
no
[Lonely music]
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
Oh, this is really funny.
What kind of president do you think he is?
(Vincenzo)
Maybe a fool is guarding
I would have ordered it to be strengthened.
I'm also prepared for any misfortune.
It's about defending your biggest weakness.
Then grab Jang Han-seo and
I didn't hear the answer
(Chayoung)
Who the hell is stupid?
Wow, Mr.
(Joosung)
Lawyer!
I just heard the news
[nervous music]
Director Gil Jong-moon of Haemun Hospital
Requesting personal protection from the prosecution
They say they're protecting me
Request for personal protection? why?
(Joosung)
I don't know, the reason hasn't been revealed.
Looks like you're trying to deal something big?
Who is the prosecutor in charge?
Prosecutor Jeong In-guk.
Well, whatever it is
I'm sure it has something to do with Babel.
I'll look into Prosecutor Jeong's side right now.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, boss.
yes
[Exciting music]
(Vincenzo)
Thank you for your hard work on the long journey.
(President Cho)
Don't say anything
Wang Xiaolin's pupil scan data
I was glad I stayed
The hacking team also took care of it quickly.
I solved the most difficult thing
(President Cho)
yes
Now just lift the top of the secret room entrance.
Just open the door right away
(Vincenzo)
To remove concrete countertops
It won't be a big shock, right?
The concrete is also thin.
It has a cut that makes it easy to take it out.
It's good
So let's start working now.
Well, to start with
I need to get the pharmacist out first.
[Exciting music]
(Chae Shin)
Welcome
(Vincenzo)
Ah, yes, monk.
(Chae Shin)
Ah, the piano teacher
You converted to Buddhism
Ah, yes
I'll just go in now
yes
[moktak sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
Ah, yes
[Interesting music]
[Miri puts on her shoes]
Why are you telling us to leave here alone?
So do other people
The monks might be in danger.
I like it
We're fine, lawyer.
Not in Seoul, but somewhere with good air.
We can also move the temple
The lawyer told us
You gave me courage and enlightenment
(dropping)
No matter what happens we
Nanyaksa Temple and Plaza here
I will protect it
[laughter]
[Jeokha’s laughter]
(Chae Shin)
Have some sweet potatoes, lawyer.
[Lonely music]
[moktak sound effect]
[Chae-shin’s embarrassed groan]
[Meaningful music]
(in advance)
Are you trying to send out the pharmacist?
If so
Maybe?
(Seunghyuk)
No matter how much I think about it
Jang Jun-woo, boy
I jumped over the line with a triple jump.
It's okay to cross the line
[Meaningful music]
It's better to get over it for sure
Sister
[Seunghyuk sighs]
(Seunghyuk)
Attorney Choi
We too can be in danger
What came into the tiger’s mouth
When is it?
You're once again sounding like it's dangerous.
Ha, so
[The door clicks open]
[Seunghyuk’s embarrassed groan]
[Myunghee clears her throat]
[nervous music]
(Seunghyuk)
Meeting, Chairman
[Seunghyuk’s embarrassed laughter]
Oh, I work too hard
(Junwoo)
Oh my
Because of what happened yesterday, my boss
It must have become very awkward
(Seunghyuk)
Oh no, I
Respect for the Chairman
So much
I think it's because it's increasing.
What the district prosecutor must do right away
There is one
Could you tell me?
please speak
[Music that heightens tension]
[Siren sounds]
[Sunam’s powerful moans]
(Seokdo)
Hey, Sunam
Did you check in there?
It might be something useful.
Please check and throw it away
Ana, really
(Sunam)
Oh, let's just call someone.
(Miss Miss)
Boss, let’s show off some style.
What is this?
Why are you looking at people like this, huh?
I feel grateful that I survived.
(Seokdo)
And save money
You have to save and save and save again!
All the money was lost and saved up
I barely got it, these are real
[growling sound]
[Seokdo is grumbling]
(Sunam)
Baby, I'm hungry
[Picks up a trash bag]
I’ll order some black bean noodles.
(Seokdo)
Hey, raise the water! I'll buy you Chapagetti
(Heesu)
What is this?
Why is there a sudden opening atmosphere?
(Larry Kang)
What are they doing here?
Boy, you have to separate waste properly, this
(Sunam)
No, what
(Seokdo)
Hey, hey!
uh?
I won't fight with you
I quit Ant Company, I won’t do anything bad!
(Larry Kang)
dog stops pooping
Hey, aren't you going out quickly?
(Sunam)
child
We're going to do other business here.
- travel agency
- (Hee-su) Travel agency?
What kind of travel agency is this?
What, what, a travel agency sending Hwangcheongil?
No, a real travel agency.
- Bye bye!
- (Sunam) Balloon!
[Interesting music]
(Larry Kang)
What is the name of the company ‘Bye Bye Balloon’?
Kids, money, pay the money
You are doing it, yes?
Oh, I have to pay merchant dues.
(Seokdo)
This isn't yours
Don't worry, I'll use it too.
Ana, really
(Hongsik)
Hey there
What are you doing here?
What, did you come to poop?
Really, really me
(Hongsik)
Oh my, I’m surprised, what is this girl?
(Sunam)
Baby, do your business, do your business
[Sunam’s annoying groan]
(Hongsik)
Oh my, it's a surprise, it's done
Stop talking, okay? Talk to me
[Hee-su mutters]
Talk to me, talk to me for a moment
Oh, come to work, stop talking.
[Cheolwook clears his throat]
(Cheolwook)
yes, yes
(Heesu)
You came
- (Hongsik) Oh, are you here?
- (Cheolwook) Yes
(Hongsik)
Ahn, please sit down for a moment...
(Kiseok)
I know everything
(Toto)
To me, he is already like a family member.
I told you everything
Hey, the number of people I know has increased again.
(Toto)
Monks also get gold
What you are looking for,
Ahn probably saw it, I guess?
[The enemy clears his throat]
[moktak sound effect]
(Hongsik)
kid, what
This is what happened
Well, don't deceive each other.
Ah, what are neighbors doing now?
You're willing to go to great lengths to find it alone.
I see the boss
You're looking for it the hardest, what are you looking for?
(Larry Kang)
Baby, we, we just, that
Let's find it together
Okay, I'll share it equally with whoever finds it.
I also wrote a memorandum
[Interesting music]
Still, the person who found it first
Shouldn’t we have more?
Then it gets more complicated
Let's just take it as 1 in N.
(Larry Kang)
Now that I think about it, it's a little unfair.
Should we ask the lawyers then?
Which method is better?
(Chae Shin)
No, then someone who knows
Doesn't it increase further?
Well, with the two lawyers, huh?
Um, who are you, that office manager…?
Write! monk
[moktak sound effect]
Oh yes, sorry, sorry
(Cheolwook)
Ah, then what should I do with this?
[Yeonjin sighs]
(Hongsik)
Okay, let's talk about it.
The contents of the memorandum are each person's thoughts.
Now, from today, let’s be very organized.
Spread out your wings
Let’s all look for it together
(Heesu)
Okay
(Cheolwook and Yeonjin)
[Cheolwook clears his throat]
(Heesu)
No betrayal, huh?
(Anchor on TV)
Meanwhile, the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
Urgent arrest of bank presidents of two banks
They're investigating the charges.
revealed
However, for violations of the Capital Markets Act,
For more information
Not yet released
Soon, the relevant people will be summoned and investigated...
(Chayoung)
Isn’t this frame too visible?
Director Seo's death, search and seizure of two banks
Babel to threaten the District Prosecutors' Office
It becomes clear that they killed Director Seo.
Because it was like this
They must have put pressure on the banks right away.
[Joosung throws a document]
(Joosung)
maybe two banks
Soon to Babel
I think it will spread a lot.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Okay, Prosecutor Jeong In-guk has been connected.
As expected
(Chayoung)
Yes, hello, Prosecutor Jeong.
This is Chayoung Hong.
yes
Ah, I wanted to ask you a few questions.
I contacted you
Yes, when is a good time for you?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
I really enjoyed the performance of the two of you.
Thank you for dealing with Babel
[Calm music]
But it seems to be of no use
I feel like I'll come back to life
Babel has always been like that
But this time we must break it down
Do you have any questions about Director Gil’s requirements?
Can you tell me?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Acquittal and ban on leaving the country
I'm asking you to stop it.
maybe change your identity
I think you are planning to move abroad.
What about the statement?
It's just Babel Group and Haemun Hospital corruption.
It has been revealed
I'm weighing the barbell.
That's right
Taking time
Looks like something is being orchestrated
Prosecutor, are you behind Chairman Jang Han-seo?
What would you do if you were in power?
Are you carrying it?
Who is that?
I don't know yet
(Chayoung)
But the existence of such a being
I'm sure
Then maybe
What does that mean...
[Meaningful music]
(Director Gil)
Chairman Kook-hwan Jang
Do you know how he died?
Are there any other secrets?
[Director Gil sets down his glass]
no
(Director Gil)
I'll tell you all about this later.
Ah, you bastards!
Ah, the bastards.
Well, I can't protect him from death.
Ah, this is why I come from a prestigious family.
They say you have to be born
Oh, you guys, this
(Chayoung)
You clearly expressed it in plural, right?
You bastards, bastards?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Yes, I'm sure
Maybe both sons are Chairman Jang Guk-hwan
I don't know if it was there at the time of death.
Then who is Director Gil?
I know it
Are you stupid?
Ah, we are the real boss of Babel.
I shorten it to ‘fool’.
Ah
Perhaps Director Gil is in the safe house?
Has anyone spoken on the phone?
Records of calls made to tracking prevention lines
There is one
It was a cannon phone
(Prosecutor Jeong)
In this situation
The owner of the cannon phone must be an idiot.
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Vincenzo)
Prosecutor
To get any clues
Can we do something like a strategy?
Entrapment or fake
Are you talking about this?
(Chayoung)
Yeah, something like that.
Like a play or a show
(Prosecutor Jeong)
No
I have followed the principles so far.
If you think a little differently,
What do you think?
Deceptive investigation methods should never be used.
sorry
(employee)
Sweet potato stew was served as an appetizer.
[humorous music]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Chayoung’s refreshing groan]
(Chayoung)
Prosecutor, please drink some water.
Oh, it's okay, eat it.
[Meaningful music]
[laughter]
[Junwoo mutters]
(Chinese book)
Why are you doing this, brother?
[Junwoo laughs]
It's nothing
What's urgent?
This time, I will be a proper younger brother.
I took the chance
[Meaningful music]
[Snaps fingers]
(Junwoo)
[English]
Mr. Johnson
Babel is Korea
We'll make it a paradise for painkillers.
All raw materials produced by your company
Send it to Babel
Our president will make it all for you!
It's banned in the US anyway, right?
What about legal issues?
(Junwoo)
Legal issues?
don't worry
I'll take care of everything, trust me.
(Buyer)
thank you
Please go to Korea
Please make it a paradise for painkillers.
(Chinese book)
[Korean]
Large investment coming in next week
firstly
Our Babel Pharmaceutical RDU-90 production
We will resume in earnest
And the last raw material import volume
We will increase production by importing three times more.
First of all, the security of the raw material warehouse
Reinforce three times more than before
(Chayoung)
'Dongil Bank, Taesan Bank
‘Large-scale investment in Babel Group’?
[Chayoung laughs]
The lawyer was right.
Evil is really resilient.
(Joosung)
Eventually, that damn RDU-90 will come out.
(Chayoung)
That's what my father tried to stop.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Ah…
I guess today is the day you’re going on a trip.
(Victim’s family 1)
Internet Jirashi Contents
Wouldn't it be better if I didn't tell you?
I'll tell you after my trip.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
Yes, Prosecutor Jeong.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
I guess Director Gil
Looks like I'm leaning towards barbell
They deny the charges one by one.
(Chayoung)
Actually, that's what I expected.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
That's why
The operation you mentioned last time
Is it still valid?
(Chayoung)
Yes, designing neatly is
This is our specialty
The timing will be tonight
I'm going against my principles and asking you a favor.
Yes, once the design is done
We will contact you right away
(Prosecutor Jeong)
yes
[Call end sound]
(Chayoung)
Well, the script is simple.
Plan A, Babel sent us
Pretending to be a killer
Induce confession to the truth
(Joosung)
Plan B
I get a thrush and am immediately confessed.
[Meaningful music]
Let's go to plan A.
Prosecutor Jeong
There will be plainclothes police officers out there.
Didn't you?
That's right, time has passed
Let's go to the entrance first.
(Joosung)
Hey there
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Joosung and Chayoung moan in surprise]
[Joosung’s trembling breathing]
[Chayoung’s surprised gasp]
(Joosung)
This, this
What happened to this?
dead
(Chayoung)
Director Gil, where is Director Gil?
[Meaningful music]
[sigh]
we are late
[surprised moan]
Lawyer
(Victim’s family 1)
Attorney, I'm sorry.
We are all saddened by the loss of our family.
I can't get over my anger today.
So I'm going to make a foolish choice
Please understand
[nervous music]
[Meaningful music]
[Gun clangs]
"Babel"
[Siren sounds]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[camera shutter sound]
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
This isn't a matter of justice to me
[Detective groans in pain]
What I have kept so far
It's a question of rules.
(Chayoung)
I will withdraw the principle
[Detective yells]
(Junwoo)
God is hiding
Giving all misfortune to humans
You enjoy it, right?
(Junwoo)
Is this fun?
(Chayoung)
How do we find the killer?
[Seunghyuk’s scream]
If it's hard to find, you have to find it.
(Chinese book)
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
(Junwoo)
That mafia
The best consiglieri?
(Chayoung)
The identity of the lawyer over there
Do you know?
(Junwoo)
Now we have to kill them, if we let them we'll die
(Chayoung)
I think something dangerous will happen
(Vincenzo)
I figured it out
The real boss of Babel
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won